Guide to the Helen and Kurt Wolff Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Subject Files, 1932-1994; Series VI; 1.25' (3 boxes)
  - INDIVIDUALS AND ORGANIZATIONS
    - Schulz, Walter, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2336)
    - Schütz, Stefan, 1986 May 26 (Box 79, Folder 2337)
    - Sieburg, Friedrich, 1952 May 1
    - Simenon, Georges, 1960-93, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2338)
    - Simon and Schuster Inc., 1960 Sep 10 (Box 79, Folder 2339)
    - Singer, Isaac Bashevis, 1978 Aug 13 (Box 79, Folder 2340)
      Includes review of Shosha by Andrei Codrescu
    - Spater, George A., 1984 Jun 15 (Box 79, Folder 2341)
    - Sternheim, Carl, 1961 Jul
    - Stifter, Adalbert, 1961 Nov 18 (Box 79, Folder 2342)
    - Suhrkamp Verlag, 1975 Oct 11
    - Tagore, Rabindranath, 1961, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2343)
    - Tau, Max, 1962 Jan 10 (Box 79, Folder 2344)
    - Tenhaeff, W. H. C. (Wilhelm Heinrich Carl), n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2345)
    - Thoma, Ludwig, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2346)
    - Thorwald, Jürgen, 1962 Oct 10 (Box 79, Folder 2347)
    - Tomasi di Lampedusa, Giuseppe, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 2348)
    - Torberg, Friedrich, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 2349)
    - Unwin, Stanley, Sir, 1960 (Box 79, Folder 2350)
    - Verlag Klaus Wagenbach, 1965-89, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2351)
    - Vigevani, Alberto, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 2352)
    - Villiers, Marjorie, 1982 (Box 79, Folder 2353)
    - Voss, Norbert, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2354)
    - Walter, Otto F. [(Otto Friedrich)?], n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2355)
    - Weiss, Peter, 1966 Feb 7 (Box 79, Folder 2356)
    - Wilhelm, Richard, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2357)
    - William Collins Sons & Co., 1959-76 (Box 79, Folder 2358)
    - Wilson, Edmund, 1962 Jun 2 (Box 79, Folder 2359)
    - Wolff, Helen, 1978-89 (Box 79, Folder 2360)
    - Wolff, Kurt, 1924-93, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2361)
    - Zeller, Bernhard, 1983 Aug 8 (Box 79, Folder 2362)
    - Zimmer, Christiane, 1987, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2363)
    - Zotos, Stephanos, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2364)
  - TOPICS
    - Expressionism, 1948-62, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2365)
    - Neustadt International Prize for Literature, 1982-85, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2366)
    - Publishing, 1925-92, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2367-2370)
    - Translation, 1961-85, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2371)
    - Other topics, 1951-63, n.d. (Box 79, Folder 2372)
- Personal Papers, 1925-1985; Series VII; 0.42' (1 box)
  Series VII, Personal Papers, is arranged alpbhabetically by material type.
  - Bibliography of Kurt Wolff correspondence (Box 80, Folder 2373)
  - Brochures and programs, 1976-77, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 2374)
  - Business cards and addresses (Box 80, Folder 2375)
  - Die Chronik von Sankt Luisen, 1925 (Box 80, Folder 2376)
  - Clippings, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 2377)
  - Contract with Verlag Heinrich Scheffler, 1964, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 2378)
  - Corrections to unidentified galleys, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 2379)
  - Hallmark Gallery Exhibition Catalog, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 2380)
  - Katalog der Incunabeln-Sammlung Kurt Wolff, [1926?] (Box 80, Folder 2381)
  - "Kurt Wolff / Bibliographie", n.d. (Box 80, Folder 2382)
  - List of "Bücher in den Verlagen Kurt Wolffs" (Box 80, Folder 2383)
  - List of "Estimated Prices for the Auction Sale of Incunables...", 1926 (Box 80, Folder 2384)
  - List of Publications of the St. John's Book Shop, [ca. 1941] (Box 80, Folder 2385)
  - List of trade salesmen, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 2386)
  - Material relating to G.E.I. award, 1984 (Box 80, Folder 2387)
  - Material relating to Goethe award, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 2388)
  - Material relating to P.E.N. award, 1977-78 (Box 80, Folder 2389)
  - Miscellaneous notes, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 2390)
  - Notes on book projects, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2391)
  - Photograph of Anne Morrow Lindbergh, [1956] (Box 80, Folder 2392)
  - Portraits of Kurt Wolff and others by Max Ludwig
  - Printed badges, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 2393)
  - Publication announcement for Alles um Liebe by Herbert Elenberg, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 2394)
  - "Quotations from actual letters received by public welfare...", n.d. (Box 80, Folder 2395)
  - Radcliffe Publishing Procedures Course, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 2396-2397)
  - Unidentified galley proofs, corrected, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 2398)
- Additional Material, 1943-1992; Series VIII; 0.63' (2 boxes)
  Series VIII, Additional Material, consists of collection material found following the completion of processing in 2007. There is additional correspondence, Harcourt Brace Jovanovich papers, writings, subject files, and personal papers.
  - CORRESPONDENCE
    - Correspondence, 1959-1975, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2872)
  - HARCOURT BRACE JAVONOVICH PAPERS
    - Papers, 1962-1971 (Box 90, Folder 2873)
  - WRITINGS
    - Auden, W. H.
      - "Old People's Home," poem, printed version, photocopy, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2874)
    - Eisenreich, Herbert
      - "Der Roman als Wissenschaft," article, printed version, Forum, 1969 Sep (Box 90, Folder 2875)
    - Gide, André
      - Interviews imaginaires, printed version, with manuscript annotations, 1943 (Box 90, Folder 2876)
    - Jaspers, Karl
      - "What Is Man?" article, printed version, Universitas, 1965 (Box 90, Folder 2877)
    - Kapscinski, Ryszard
      - "1945," article, printed version, The New Republic, photocopy, 1986 Jan 27 (Box 90, Folder 2878)
    - Ried, Tessa
      - [Questions?], typescript, photocopy, [circa 1986] (Box 90, Folder 2879)
    - Schiff, Stephen
      - "The Years of Living Dangerously," article, printed version, Vanity Fair, photocopy, 1991 Mar (Box 90, Folder 2880)
    - Vennewitz, Leila
      - "The Art of the Other," lecture, typescript, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 2881)
    - Woods, John E.
      - Review of Evening Edged in Gold by Arno Schmidt, typescript, photocopy, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2882)
    - Unidentified
      - "Kurt Wolff," essay, typescript, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2883)
      - Review of The Waterfalls of Slunj, typescript, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2884)
  - SUBJECT FILES
    - Balakian, Nona, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2885)
    - Eliade, Mircea, 1972-1979, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2886)
    - Feltrinelli, Giangiacomo, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2887)
    - Frisch, Karl von, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2888)
    - Jacobi, Jolande, 1964, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2889)
    - Jaspers, Karl, 1961-1974, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2890-2892)
    - Johnson, Uwe, 1975-1992, n.d. (Box 90, Folder 2893-2895)
    - Kapusinski, Ryszard, 1983, 1985 (Box 91, Folder 2896)
    - Konrád, György, 1982-1986, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 2897)
    - Lem, Stanislaw, 1981-1984 (Box 91, Folder 2898)
    - Lindbergh, Charles, 1960-1987 (Box 91, Folder 2899)
    - Lorenz, Konrad, 1965, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 2900)
    - Mann, Thomas, 1951-1963, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 2901)
    - Mellon, Paul, 1963 Oct 5 (Box 91, Folder 2902)
    - Pieper, Josef, 1963-1966, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 2903)
    - Read, Herbert Edward, 1959-1960 (Box 91, Folder 2904)
    - Rowohlt, Ernest, 1960 (Box 91, Folder 2905)
  - PERSONAL PAPERS
    - List of journals, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 2906)
    - Manuscript material, n.d. (Box 91, Folder 2907)
- Oversize, 1925-1994; 5.01' (3 boxes)
  - Financial statements for Kurt Wolff Verlag (In Series II), 1925-26 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2399)
  - Publicity for Doctor Zhivago by Boris Leonidovich Pasternak (In Series III), 1958-59, n.d. (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2400)
  - Provision for Profit Sharing Plan (In Series III), 1957 Apr 30 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2401)
  - Statements of Pantheon income and expenses (In Sseries III), 1960, n.d. (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2402)
  - Review of Marie Bonaparte by Celia Bertin (In Series IV), 1982 Dec 16 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2403)
  - Review of Mr. Palomar by Italo Calvino (In Series IV), 1985 Sep 29 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2404)
  - Review of Under the Jaguar Sun by Italo Calvino (In Series IV) (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2405)
  - Review of After the Fires by Peter Demetz (In Series IV), 1986 Dec 28 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2406)
  - Brief mention of The Name of the Rose by Umberto Eco (In Series IV), 1983 Jul 17 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2407)
  - Reviews of The Call of the Toad by Günter Grass (In Series IV), 1992, n.d. (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2408)
  - Publicity for Dog Years ) by Günter Grass (In Series IV), [1963?] (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2409)
  - Reviews of The Flounder by Günter Grass (In Series IV), 1978-79 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2410)
  - Reviews of The Rat by Günter Grass (In Series IV), 1986-87 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2410a)
  - Reviews of Show Your Tongue by Günter Grass (In Series IV), 1989 May 21 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2411)
  - Review of Richard Wagner, his Life, his Work, his Century by Martin Gregor-Dellin (In Series IV), 1983 Jun 17 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2412)
  - Review of The West Bank Story by Rafik Halabi (In Series IV), 1982 May 16 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2412a)
  - Review of Another Day of Life by Ryszard Kapuscinski (In Series IV), 1987 Feb 15 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2412b)
  - Publicity for Dearly Beloved by Anne Morrow Lindbergh (In Series IV), 1962 Jun 13 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2413)
  - Review of The Daughters of Karl Marx by Jenny Marx Longuet (In Series IV), 1982 May 2 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2414)
  - Reviews of Marthe (In Series IV), 1984-85 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2414a)
  - Reviews of A Need to Testify by Iris Origo (In Series IV), 1984 Aug (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2415)
  - Reviews of Black Box by Amos Oz (In Series IV), [1988?] (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2416)
  - Reviews of Im Lande Israel by Amos Oz (In Series IV), 1985 Mar 29 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2417)
  - Review of A Vanished Present by Aleksandr Leonidovich Pasternak (In Series IV), 1985 Jul 21 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2417a)
  - Review of The Correspondence of Boris Pasternak and Olga Friedenberg, 1910- 1954 by Boris Pasternak (In Series IV), 1982 Jun 27 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2417b)
  - Review of The Persistence of Unifying Patterns by Elémire Zolla (In Series IV) (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2418)
  - Clippings on Karl Kraus (In Series V), 1954, 1962 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2419)
  - Clipping on Lou Andreas-Salomé (In Series V), 1963 May 5 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2419a)
  - Letter to the editor from Hannah Arendt (In Series V), 1963 Jun 23 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2420)
  - Article by Ernst H. Gombrich in Literatur und Kunst (In Series V), 1983 Jun 25 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2421)
  - Article by Günter Grass in Die Zeit (In Series V), 1991 Jun 14 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2422)
  - Article by Günter Grass (In Series V), 1982 Oct 1 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2422a)
  - Article by Ninon Hesse in Neue Zürcher Zeitung (In Series V), 1960 Apr 3 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2423)
  - Article by Jolande Jacobi in Neue Zürcher Zeitung (In Series V), 1956 May 6 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2424)
  - Article by Carl Gustav Jung (In Series V) (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2425)
  - Article by Bartolomeo Migone (In Series V) (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2426)
  - Article by Amoz Oz (In Series V), 1982 Jul 11 (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2427)
  - Article by Larry Rivers (In Series V), n.d. (Box 81 (Oversize), Folder 2428)
  - Clipping on Alfred A. Knopf, Inc. (In Series VI), 1960 Jun 2 (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2429)
  - Clippings on Hannah Arendt (In Series VI) (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2430)
  - Clipping on Walter Benjamin (In Series VI) (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2431)
  - Review of Italy and the English Romantics by C. P. Brand, 1958 Jan 3 (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2432)
  - Clippings on Hermann Broch (In Series VI) (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2433)
  - Clippings on Max Brod (In Series VI), 1960 Dec 30 (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2433a)
  - Clippings on Italo Calvino (In Series VI) (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2434)
  - Clipping on Jean Cocteau (In Series VI), 1984 May 13 (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2435)
  - Clipping on Lawrence Durrell (In Series VI) (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2436)
  - Clippings on Feltrinelli (In Series VI), 1961-72 (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2436a)
  - Clippings on Max Frisch (In Series VI), 1983-92 (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2437)
  - Clippings on Günter Grass (In Series VI), 1967-93, n.d. (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2438)
  - Clippings on Friedrich Gundolf (In Series VI), 1962-63 (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2439)
  - Clipping on Willy Haas (In Series VI), 1961 Jun 7 (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2440)
  - Review of A Moment of True Feeling by Peter Handke (In Series VI), 1977 Jul 31 (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2441)
  - Clippings on Harcourt Brace Jovanovich (In Series VI), 1987-90, n.d. (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2442)
  - Clippings on Kurd de Hardt (In Series VI) (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2443)
  - Clipping on Uwe Johnson (In Series VI), 1961 Oct 6 (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2444)
  - Clippings on Carl Gustav Jung (In Series VI), 1958-61 (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2445)
  - [Empty folder] (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2446)
  - Article on Heinrich von Kleist by Adolf Muschg (In Series VI), 1961 Nov 19 (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2447)
  - Clipping on Annette Kolb (In Series VI), 1965 Feb 2 (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2448)
  - Clipping on Anne Morrow Lindbergh (In Series VI), 1994 Feb 5 (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2449)
  - Clipping on Charles A. Lindbergh (In Series VI), 1970 Mar 11 (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2450)
  - Clipping on Konrad Lorenz (In Series VI) (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2451)
  - Clippings on Ralph Manheim (In Series VI) (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2452)
  - Article on Thomas Mann by Carl Helbling (In Series VI), 1961 Dec 17 (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2453)
  - Review of Matthias' Ich war Tucholskys Lottchen (In Series VI), 1962 May 4 (Box 82 (Oversize), Folder 2454)
  - Clipping on Paul Mellon (In Series VI), n.d. (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2455)
  - Clipping on Philippe de Montebello (In Series VI), 1985 Nov 3 (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2456)
  - Clipping on Jan Morris (In Series VI), 1974 Mar 17 (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2457)
  - Clippings on Robert Neumann (In Series VI) (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2458)
  - Clipping on Iris Origo (In Series VI), 1982 Apr 30 (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2459)
  - Clippings on Amos Oz (In Series VI), 1987, 1992 (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2460)
  - Clippings on Pantheon Books (In Series VI) (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2461)
  - Clippings on Boris Pasternak (In Series VI) (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2462)
  - Clipping on Random House (In Series VI) (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2463)
  - Clipping on Erich Maria Remarque (In Series VI), 1962 Dec 1 (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2464)
  - Clipping on Marcel Röthlisberger (In Series VI), 1963 May 31 (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2465)
  - Clippings on Denis de Rougemont (In Series VI), 1960-61 (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2466)
  - Clipping on Steven Runciman (In Series VI) (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2467)
  - Clipping on George Saiko (In Series VI), 1986 Feb 7 (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2468)
  - Clipping on Salman Schocken (In Series VI) (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2469)
  - Clipping on Wilhelm von Scholz (In Series VI), 1950 Jul 15 (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2469a)
  - Clipping on Friedrich Sieburg (In Series VI), 1952 May 1 (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2470)
  - Clippings on Georges Simenon (In Series VI) (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2471)
  - Clipping on Carl Sternheim (In Series VI) (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2472)
  - Clipping on Suhrkamp Verlag (In Series VI) (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2473)
  - Clippings on Helen Wolff (In Series VI), 1984-85 (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2474)
  - Clippings on Kurt Wolff (In Series VI), 1963, 1993 (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2475)
  - Clippings on Expressionism (In Series VI) (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2475a)
  - Clippings on publishing (In Series VI), 1956-87, n.d. (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2476)
  - Clippings on translation (In Series VI), 1961-62 (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2477)
  - Clippings on other topics (In Series VI) (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2478)
  - Portraits of Kurt Wolff and others by Max Ludwig (In Series VII) (Box 83 (Oversize), Folder 2479)
- Restricted Fragile Papers, 2.09' (5 boxes)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, folder 7 (Box 84, Folder 2480)
  - Box 1, folder 26 (Box 84, Folder 2481)
  - Box 1, folder 29 (Box 84, Folder 2482)
  - Box 1, folder 30 (Box 84, Folder 2483)
  - Box 2, folder 37 (Box 84, Folder 2484)
  - Box 2, folder 43 (Box 84, Folder 2485)
  - Box 2, folder 47 (Box 84, Folder 2486)
  - Box 2, folder 67 (Box 84, Folder 2487)
  - Box 2, folder 80 (Box 84, Folder 2488)
  - Box 2, folder 81 (Box 84, Folder 2489)
  - Box 2, folder 84 (Box 84, Folder 2490)
  - Box 2, folder 89 (Box 84, Folder 2491)
  - Box 2, folder 91 (Box 84, Folder 2492)
  - Box 2, folder 93 (Box 84, Folder 2493)
  - Box 3, folder 95 (Box 84, Folder 2494)
  - Box 3, folder 102 (Box 84, Folder 2495)
  - Box 3, folder 103 (Box 84, Folder 2496)
  - Box 3, folder 104 (Box 84, Folder 2497)
  - Box 3, folder 105 (Box 84, Folder 2498)
  - Box 3, folder 106 (Box 84, Folder 2499)
  - Box 3, folder 107 (Box 84, Folder 2500)
  - Box 3, folder 125 (Box 84, Folder 2501)
  - Box 3, folder 135 (Box 84, Folder 2502)
  - Box 3, folder 136 (Box 84, Folder 2503)
  - Box 4, folder 174 (Box 84, Folder 2504)
  - Box 4, folder 175 (Box 84, Folder 2505)
  - Box 4, folder 176 (Box 84, Folder 2506)
  - Box 4, folder 190 (Box 84, Folder 2507)
  - Box 4, folder 191 (Box 84, Folder 2508)
  - Box 4, folder 192 (Box 84, Folder 2509)
  - Box 4, folder 199 (Box 84, Folder 2510)
  - Box 4, folder 207 (Box 84, Folder 2511)
  - Box 5, folder 221 (Box 84, Folder 2512)
  - Box 5, folder 226 (Box 84, Folder 2513)
  - Box 5, folder 227 (Box 84, Folder 2514)
  - Box 5, folder 228 (Box 84, Folder 2515)
  - Box 5, folder 231 (Box 84, Folder 2516)
  - Box 5, folder 232 (Box 84, Folder 2517)
  - Box 5, folder 236 (Box 84, Folder 2518)
  - Box 5, folder 247 (Box 84, Folder 2519)
  - Box 5, folder 249 (Box 84, Folder 2520)
  - Box 6, folder 259 (Box 84, Folder 2521)
  - Box 6, folder 260 (Box 84, Folder 2522)
  - Box 6, folder 263 (Box 84, Folder 2523)
  - Box 6, folder 264 (Box 84, Folder 2524)
  - Box 6, folder 265 (Box 84, Folder 2525)
  - Box 6, folder 266 (Box 84, Folder 2526)
  - Box 6, folder 267 (Box 84, Folder 2527)
  - Box 6, folder 269 (Box 84, Folder 2528)
  - Box 6, folder 274 (Box 84, Folder 2529)
  - Box 7, folder 295 (Box 84, Folder 2530)
  - Box 7, folder 300 (Box 84, Folder 2531)
  - Box 7, folder 301 (Box 84, Folder 2532)
  - Box 7, folder 306 (Box 84, Folder 2533)
  - Box 7, folder 309 (Box 84, Folder 2534)
  - Box 7, folder 316 (Box 84, Folder 2535)
  - Box 7, folder 317 (Box 84, Folder 2536)
  - Box 7, folder 319 (Box 84, Folder 2537)
  - Box 7, folder 321 (Box 84, Folder 2538)
  - Box 7, folder 324 (Box 84, Folder 2539)
  - Box 8, folder 331 (Box 84, Folder 2540)
  - Box 8, folder 332 (Box 84, Folder 2541)
  - Box 8, folder 347 (Box 84, Folder 2542)
  - Box 8, folder 350 (Box 84, Folder 2543)
  - Box 8, folder 351 (Box 84, Folder 2544)
  - Box 8, folder 353 (Box 84, Folder 2545)
  - Box 8, folder 354 (Box 84, Folder 2546)
  - Box 9, folder 355 (Box 84, Folder 2547)
  - Box 9, folder 363 (Box 84, Folder 2548)
  - Box 9, folder 372 (Box 84, Folder 2549)
  - Box 9, folder 374 (Box 84, Folder 2550)
  - Box 9, folder 377 (Box 84, Folder 2551)
  - Box 10, folder 385 (Box 84, Folder 2552)
  - Box 10, folder 392 (Box 84, Folder 2553)
  - Box 10, folder 394 (Box 84, Folder 2554)
  - Box 10, folder 395 (Box 84, Folder 2555)
  - Box 10, folder 396 (Box 84, Folder 2556)
  - Box 10, folder 397 (Box 84, Folder 2557)
  - Box 10, folder 398 (Box 84, Folder 2558)
  - Box 10, folder 399 (Box 84, Folder 2559)
  - Box 10, folder 400 (Box 84, Folder 2560)
  - Box 10, folder 401 (Box 84, Folder 2561)
  - Box 10, folder 402 (Box 84, Folder 2562)
  - Box 10, folder 403 (Box 84, Folder 2563)
  - Box 11, folder 404 (Box 85, Folder 2564)
  - Box 11, folder 405 (Box 85, Folder 2565)
  - Box 11, folder 406 (Box 85, Folder 2566)
  - Box 11, folder 407 (Box 85, Folder 2567)
  - Box 11, folder 408 (Box 85, Folder 2568)
  - Box 11, folder 409 (Box 85, Folder 2569)
  - Box 11, folder 410 (Box 85, Folder 2570)
  - Box 11, folder 411 (Box 85, Folder 2571)
  - Box 11, folder 414 (Box 85, Folder 2572)
  - Box 11, folder 416 (Box 85, Folder 2573)
  - Box 11, folder 418 (Box 85, Folder 2574)
  - Box 11, folder 419 (Box 85, Folder 2575)
  - Box 12, folder 420 (Box 85, Folder 2576)
  - Box 12, folder 421 (Box 85, Folder 2577)
  - Box 12, folder 424 (Box 85, Folder 2578)
  - Box 12, folder 425 (Box 85, Folder 2579)
  - Box 12, folder 426 (Box 85, Folder 2580)
  - Box 12, folder 427 (Box 85, Folder 2581)
  - Box 12, folder 429 (Box 85, Folder 2582)
  - Box 13, folder 437 (Box 85, Folder 2583)
  - Box 14, folder 469 (Box 85, Folder 2584)
  - Box 14, folder 471 (Box 85, Folder 2585)
  - Box 14, folder 472 (Box 85, Folder 2586)
  - Box 14, folder 474 (Box 85, Folder 2587)
  - Box 14, folder 475 (Box 85, Folder 2588)
  - Box 14, folder 476 (Box 85, Folder 2589)
  - Box 14, folder 478 (Box 85, Folder 2590)
  - Box 14, folder 480 (Box 85, Folder 2591)
  - Box 14, folder 481 (Box 85, Folder 2592)
  - Box 15, folder 483 (Box 85, Folder 2593)
  - Box 15, folder 484 (Box 85, Folder 2594)
  - Box 15, folder 485 (Box 85, Folder 2595)
  - Box 15, folder 489 (Box 85, Folder 2596)
  - Box 15, folder 490 (Box 85, Folder 2597)
  - Box 15, folder 491 (Box 85, Folder 2598)
  - Box 15, folder 493 (Box 85, Folder 2599)
  - Box 15, folder 497 (Box 85, Folder 2600)
  - Box 16, folder 506 (Box 85, Folder 2601)
  - Box 16, folder 512 (Box 85, Folder 2602)
  - Box 16, folder 516 (Box 85, Folder 2603)
  - Box 16, folder 520 (Box 85, Folder 2604)
  - Box 16, folder 524 (Box 85, Folder 2605)
  - Box 16, folder 543 (Box 85, Folder 2606)
  - Box 17, folder 548 (Box 85, Folder 2607)
  - Box 17, folder 552 (Box 85, Folder 2608)
  - Box 17, folder 558 (Box 85, Folder 2609)
  - Box 17, folder 561 (Box 85, Folder 2610)
  - Box 17, folder 570 (Box 85, Folder 2611)
  - Box 17, folder 571 (Box 85, Folder 2612)
  - Box 18, folder 576 (Box 85, Folder 2613)
  - Box 18, folder 577 (Box 85, Folder 2614)
  - Box 18, folder 578 (Box 85, Folder 2615)
  - Box 18, folder 588 (Box 85, Folder 2616)
  - Box 18, folder 592 (Box 85, Folder 2617)
  - Box 18, folder 593 (Box 85, Folder 2618)
  - Box 18, folder 594 (Box 85, Folder 2619)
  - Box 18, folder 597 (Box 85, Folder 2620)
  - Box 19, folder 598 (Box 85, Folder 2621)
  - Box 19, folder 600 (Box 85, Folder 2622)
  - Box 19, folder 601 (Box 85, Folder 2623)
  - Box 19, folder 607 (Box 85, Folder 2624)
  - Box 19, folder 614 (Box 85, Folder 2625)
  - Box 19, folder 618 (Box 85, Folder 2626)
  - Box 19, folder 619 (Box 85, Folder 2627)
  - Box 21, folder 651 (Box 85, Folder 2628)
  - Box 21, folder 652 (Box 85, Folder 2629)
  - Box 21, folder 658 (Box 85, Folder 2630)
  - Box 22, folder 667 (Box 85, Folder 2631)
  - Box 22, folder 673 (Box 85, Folder 2632)
  - Box 22, folder 678 (Box 85, Folder 2633)
  - Box 22, folder 688 (Box 85, Folder 2634)
  - Box 23, folder 707 (Box 85, Folder 2635)
  - Box 23, folder 710 (Box 85, Folder 2636)
  - Box 23, folder 715 (Box 85, Folder 2637)
  - Box 23, folder 726 (Box 85, Folder 2638)
  - Box 23, folder 728 (Box 85, Folder 2639)
  - Box 23, folder 734 (Box 85, Folder 2640)
  - Box 23, folder 735 (Box 85, Folder 2641)
  - [Empty folder] (Box 85, Folder 2642)
  - Box 23, folder 741 (Box 85, Folder 2643)
  - Box 23, folder 742 (Box 85, Folder 2644)
  - Box 23, folder 744 (Box 85, Folder 2645)
  - Box 24, folder 745 (Box 85, Folder 2646)
  - Box 24, folder 747 (Box 85, Folder 2647)
  - Box 24, folder 748 (Box 85, Folder 2648)
  - Box 24, folder 750 (Box 85, Folder 2649)
  - Box 24, folder 753 (Box 85, Folder 2650)
  - Box 24, folder 757 (Box 85, Folder 2651)
  - Box 25, folder 765 (Box 85, Folder 2652)
  - Box 25, folder 771 (Box 85, Folder 2653)